{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Stagers","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46411/":{"taskOID":46411,"originalTaskOID":46411,"setID":1378,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6775,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9503,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Staging furniture \u0026 accessories","answerDisplayText":"Staging furniture \u0026 accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9504,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"De-cluttering and staging of furniture","answerDisplayText":"De-cluttering and staging of furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9501,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Major repair, design and clutter issues","answerDisplayText":"Major repair, design and clutter issues","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9502,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Minor repair, design and clutter issues","answerDisplayText":"Minor repair, design and clutter issues","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6776,"questionDisplayText":"Listing date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When will your house go on the market?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"It's already on the market","answerDisplayText":"It's already on the market","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9506,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"As soon as possible","answerDisplayText":"As soon as possible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9507,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"When the staging is complete","answerDisplayText":"When the staging is complete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9508,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6777,"questionDisplayText":"Problem areas","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which aspects of your home need attention?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9509,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Curb appeal","answerDisplayText":"Curb appeal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9510,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Reduce clutter / organize","answerDisplayText":"Reduce clutter / organize","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9511,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9512,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walls and ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Walls and ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9513,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Built-in cabinets or furniture","answerDisplayText":"Built-in cabinets or furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9514,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Furnishings or window treatments","answerDisplayText":"Furnishings or window treatments","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6778,"questionDisplayText":"Years of residence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long have you lived in your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9515,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9516,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 years","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9517,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4 - 8 years","answerDisplayText":"4 - 8 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9518,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 8 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 8 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20655,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1 - 3 months","answerDisplayText":"1 - 3 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200406,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6775,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9503,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Staging furniture \u0026 accessories","answerDisplayText":"Staging furniture \u0026 accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9504,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"De-cluttering and staging of furniture","answerDisplayText":"De-cluttering and staging of furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9501,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Major repair, design and clutter issues","answerDisplayText":"Major repair, design and clutter issues","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9502,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Minor repair, design and clutter issues","answerDisplayText":"Minor repair, design and clutter issues","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9503,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Staging furniture \u0026 accessories","answerDisplayText":"Staging furniture \u0026 accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9504,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"De-cluttering and staging of furniture","answerDisplayText":"De-cluttering and staging of furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9501,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Major repair, design and clutter issues","answerDisplayText":"Major repair, design and clutter issues","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9502,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Minor repair, design and clutter issues","answerDisplayText":"Minor repair, design and clutter issues","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6776,"questionDisplayText":"Listing date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When will your house go on the market?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"It's already on the market","answerDisplayText":"It's already on the market","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9506,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"As soon as possible","answerDisplayText":"As soon as possible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9507,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"When the staging is complete","answerDisplayText":"When the staging is complete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9508,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9505,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"It's already on the market","answerDisplayText":"It's already on the market","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9506,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"As soon as possible","answerDisplayText":"As soon as possible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9507,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"When the staging is complete","answerDisplayText":"When the staging is complete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9508,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6777,"questionDisplayText":"Problem areas","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which aspects of your home need attention?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9509,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Curb appeal","answerDisplayText":"Curb appeal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9510,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Reduce clutter / organize","answerDisplayText":"Reduce clutter / organize","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9511,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9512,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walls and ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Walls and ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9513,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Built-in cabinets or furniture","answerDisplayText":"Built-in cabinets or furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9514,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Furnishings or window treatments","answerDisplayText":"Furnishings or window treatments","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9509,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Curb appeal","answerDisplayText":"Curb appeal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9510,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Reduce clutter / organize","answerDisplayText":"Reduce clutter / organize","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9511,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9512,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walls and ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Walls and ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9513,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Built-in cabinets or furniture","answerDisplayText":"Built-in cabinets or furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9514,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Furnishings or window treatments","answerDisplayText":"Furnishings or window treatments","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6778,"questionDisplayText":"Years of residence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long have you lived in your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9515,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9516,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 years","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9517,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4 - 8 years","answerDisplayText":"4 - 8 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9518,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 8 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 8 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9515,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9516,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 4 years","answerDisplayText":"2 - 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9517,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4 - 8 years","answerDisplayText":"4 - 8 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9518,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 8 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 8 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20655,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1 - 3 months","answerDisplayText":"1 - 3 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200406,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20655,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1 - 3 months","answerDisplayText":"1 - 3 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3 - 6 months","answerDisplayText":"3 - 6 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200406,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"6 - 12 months","answerDisplayText":"6 - 12 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/46411/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46411,"taskName":"Stage a Home","taskDescription":"Stage or Showcase a Home for Sale","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Stagers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":123,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Stage sale resale showcasing home","textMessagingName":"Stage a Home","rolloverLongDesc":"Professionals in Home Staging and Showcasing.  Can help a home seller get top dollar for their house.","rolloverShortDesc":"Specialist in home staging \u0026 showcasing.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local Home Staging Pros.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Staging \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Stage or Design a Home for Sale","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":3,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Stage a Home","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Stage a Home","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Staging Need","urlName":"Home-Staging","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Staging Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Cost \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Stage,sale,resale,showcasing,home,equipment,props,staging,storage,furniture,rental","emcCategoryOid":-12019,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project (include preferred styles, colors and textures):","primaryQuestionSetId":1378,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}